

Software Development Analyst Application Development Analyst seeking roles in Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Client Management, Process Improvement, Software Design, Project Management, C, C++, .NET



Current Designation: Application Development Analyst Total Experience: 7 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Current Company: Accenture Notice Period: 15 Days or less

Current Location: Chennai Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [Computers]

Pref. Location: Chennai

Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Software Development Analyst Application Development Analyst, Software Developer, Software Development, Application Programming, Requirement Gathering, Software Testing, Client Management, Process

Improvement, Software Design, Project Management, C, C++, . NET

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 21-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

Over 7+ years of experience in all phases of Analysis, Design, Development, Implementation.

Experience in Automation Anywhere, VBA, HP Script, Dot Net and MS SQL (8 months experience).

Experience in gathering requirements from clients and preparing Design Documents.

Experience in creating unit test plan and unit test cases based on technical specifications.

Strong knowledge in Technical knowledge and problem solving.

Capable of working as an individual as well as a part of team.

Work Experience

Accenture solutions Pvt.Ltd as Software Development Analyst, Application Development Analyst Nov 2017 to Aug 2020

Adecco India Pvt.Ltd as Software Engineer Nov 2015 to Oct 2017

Accenture as Application Development Analyst Nov 2015 to Till Date

Computers International as Junior Software Engineer Jun 2013 to Oct 2015

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (Computers) from Anandh institute of higher technology in 2012

IT Skills

| Skill Name | Version Last Used Experience |
|----------------------------------|------------------------------|
| C, C++ | |
| DotNet, VBA | |
| Automation Anywhere, Phantom FTE | |
| HP Script | |
| MS SQL | |
| Windows 7, Windows 8, Windows 10 | |

Affirmative Action

Work Authorization

Employment Status: Full time

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No